Lord Farquaad arrived on horseback and proposed to Fiona on the spot.
She barely had time to think.
The wedding was set for that very afternoon.
This is happening too fast.
Smile, my soon-to-be queen.
We'll be married by sunset.
I don't even know you.
You'll learn to love me.
Meanwhile, Shrek had returned to his empty swamp feeling utterly miserable.
Donkey followed him there and refused to let him give up.
You messed up big time, Shrek.
She's a princess. I'm an ogre.
She actually likes you, you know.
Someone like her can't like me.
Why not? You're a good person.
I have layers, remember?
So does she. Go get her.
It might be too late.
Then we better hurry up.
They called on the dragon, who was very happy to help.
Together, they flew toward Duloc as fast as they possibly could.
I have to tell her something.
Tell her exactly how you feel.
I've never done this before.
Neither have I. Just be honest.
Just be honest.
What do I even say?
Say exactly how you feel.
What if she says no?
What if she says yes?
You know what? You're right.
For the record, I knew it.